Previously, on Friends:
17 hours I have been at this.
How many centimeters
am I dilated?
Three.
Just three?
I'm dilated three.
We've always talked about
having a baby someday.
So, we're going to try?
Right here?
No, not here.
Maybe here.
This is your grandmother's
engagement ring.
I want you to give it
to Rachel.
Mom, no.
Ross, this isn't
just some girl
you picked up in a bar
and... humped.
Hey, uh, I take it you're
just visiting someone?
Uh-huh, yeah.
Want to visit someone else?
Oh, yeah, I would like that.
( gasps )
That's him.
Great. Well, go get him.
Or maybe you could go in first.
Hi.
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray.
I have a few
routine questions.
Do you sleep with women
and never call them again?
Oh...
my... God!
( gasps )
Oh.
( both moaning )
Should we tell Rachel
there's an empty
private room right
next door to hers?
We could...
or we could have sex
in it.
Well, let me
think about that...
while I remove
my pants.
Okay, mister.
Fertilize me.
( Janice laughing )
Does that sound
like Janice?
If it's not,
then there's
two of them
and that would
mean it's the
end of the world.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
ROSS:
Oh, hi.
I can't believe
this is taking so long.
How are you doing?
Oh, not bad.
You know that feeling
when you're trying
to blow a Saint Bernard
out your ass?
The weirdest thing.
Did I hear...?
Mother of God, it's true.
Chandler Bing!
( laughs )
J-Janice.
Not just Janice.
Janice in labor.
Contracting and everything.
Oh, this should be easy.
I have a very wide pelvis.
You remember, Chandler?
( laughs )
Janice, I didn't even know
you were pregnant.
Who's the... unwitting human
whose essence you've stolen?
It's you.
This is yours.
What?!
( laughs )
Look how nervous he gets.
We haven't slept together
in years.
( laughs )
That's funny.
Does it hurt?
Does the labor hurt?
Okay, I've got one
for you.
Yeah.
If you had to,
which would you rather eat--
a seeing eye dog,
or a talking gorilla?
That's a good one.
Mm-hmm.
I'd have to say...
the talking gorilla
'cause at least
I could explain to him
that you're making me eat him.
Oh. Somebody went to college.
Yeah.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just
my foot itches like crazy.
Oh. I'll get it.
Wow.
I usually get
to know a girl better
before I let her spoon me.
Relax. It's not like
we're forking.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!!
Oh, that's five, Ross.
Five women have had five babies,
and I have had no babies.
Why doesn't she want
to come out?
You know what
I think it is?
I think you made such
a nice home for her
over the last
nine months
that she just doesn't
want to leave.
Oh.
Look at you
making up crap for me.
Oh, God.
Ooh, ooh.
Okay, okay.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Oh.
21 hours.
You're a hero.
Doctor, you got
to do something.
You got to give me drugs
or you got to light a fire
up in there
and just smoke it out.
Actually
I think you're ready
to go to the delivery room.
What?
Ten centimeters.
You're about to become a mom.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Ha, ha, ha. Beat you, sucker.
Oh, my God.
That's the doctor
who was in my room before.
Huh.
Okay, Mr. Percocet.
I'm telling you
the guy from that show was here
in my room
asking me all these
weird questions.
Cliff
do you really believe
that a character
from a TV show was here
in your room?
Rachel's having her baby!
That-that's him.
You know him?
Okay, okay.
I... okay.
Um, this...
I-I sent my friend
Joey in here
to find out
stuff about you.
Um, but, you know,
if it helps
you came off great.
A lot better than I'm
coming off right now.
I don't believe this.
You got him to pretend
he was some fake doctor?
Fake?
Oh, excuse me. Hello.
And then you tried
to make me think
that I was crazy?
You're right.
That was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's just that I
liked you so much.
Can we just...
can we just
start over?
I don't think so.
If I may.
Um, look, Cliff.
You told me a lot
of personal stuff
about you, right?
Now, maybe-maybe
it would help
if-if you knew some
personal stuff about her.
Uh, she was married
to a gay ice dancer.
Uh... she gave birth
to her brother's triplets.
Uh...
Oh, oh.
Her twin sister
used to do porn.
Yeah. Uh...
Joey, we're trying to
dial down the crazy.
Right.
Um...
Look, we don't...
we don't really know each other
so it would be really easy
to just forget about this, but
there seems to be something
between us
and I don't know about you
but that doesn't happen
to me a lot.
It doesn't happen to me, either.
Me neither.
Push.
( groaning ):
Oh.
That's it.
Push.
We're going to push
for five more seconds.
Five, four
three, two, one.
Oh!
( breathing heavily )
Okay, the next
contraction
should be
in about
20 seconds.
I can't.
I can't push anymore.
Sweetie, you're
doing great.
Oh, God!
20 seconds, my ass!
There we go.
Okay, keep pushing.
Come on,
come on.
Push. Wait.
I see something.
What? You do, you do?
Oh, my God!
Don't say, "Oh, my God."
"Oh, my God," what?
What is that?
It's the baby's
buttocks.
She's breech.
Oh, thank God.
I thought she had two heads.
Is she going to be okay?
She's going
to be fine.
Yeah, yeah.
She's in a more
difficult position
so you're going to
have to push even
harder now. Go.
Go, go.
That's it.
Push, push.
Rachel, you're going to have
to push even harder.
Nothing's
happening.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Yes, you can.
No, I can't.
Hey, hey, come
on, you can.
I know you can
do this. Let's go.
I can't. No, I can't.
Please, you do it for me.
No. Come on.
Let's go. One
more time.
One final push.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Oh.
Good.
ROSS:
Keep pushing!
Are you okay?
Oh. You have no idea
how much this hurts.
Keep going.
Oh.
Here we go.
Oh, oh, she's
upside down
but she's coming,
she's coming.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God,
she's here.
Hi.
( Rachel crying
and laughing )
Oh, she's...
she's perfect. Oh.
RACHEL:
Wow!
Oh, she's so tiny.
Oh.
Where did she go?
Oh, it's okay.
They're just
wrapping her up.
Okay. Well, be careful
with her.
She's really tiny.
Here she is.
( crying )
Hi.
Oh, hi, you.
Oh, thanks for coming
out of me.
( crying )
I know.
Oh.
Yes. Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, she's looking at me.
Hi.
I know you.
Do we have a name yet?
No. Not yet.
That's fine.
For now we'll
just call her
Baby Girl Green.
Oh, no.
Baby Girl Geller-Green.
Hello, baby girl.
PHOEBE:
Can we come in?
Oh, come on in.
Hi.
Oh, there
she is.
PHOEBE:
Oh, she's
so beautiful.
Here.
Oh, my God.
She's amazing.
Oh... oh, I'm so glad
you guys got drunk and had sex.
It's incredible.
I mean, one minute
she's inside you
and then, 47 hours
later, here she is.
Hi.
She looks so real.
You know what I mean.
Okay, my turn,
my turn.
Aunt Phoebe.
Yes.
Oh, baby.
Ooh, oh,
you're so cute.
Oh, I could squeeze
your little head.
I won't.
( crying )
Honey, what's
the matter?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
I just can't stop crying.
The doctor said
it's completely normal
with all the hormones.
Plus, you're
sleep-deprived.
So? You guys are
all sleep-deprived.
I don't see you weeping
because you put your slippers
on the wrong feet.
Oh, God.
What's the matter now?
I was reliving it.
So, do you know what you're
going to call her yet?
Oh, wait a minute.
It's not going to be
Baby Girl?
I thought that was
so original.
Uh, actually, we've
narrowed it down to two names.
Yeah, and you know what?
I love them both.
So why don't you just pick one
and that'll be it.
Wow.
Um...
okay.
Uh... everyone
this is Isabella.
Oh, I love it.
Hi, Isabella.
( whimpering )
What?
That's not her name.
I'm sorry, she just doesn't
feel like an Isabella.
What was the
other one, Ross?
Um, Delilah.
Oh, great.
Suddenly she sounds like
a Biblical whore.
So, I guess we're
back to, uh, Baby Girl.
Yay!
What, what are
we going to do?
It's okay, honey.
You'll find
a name.
Ugh, easy for you to say.
You already know what your
kids' names are going to be.
You do?
Yeah, I had them picked out
since I was 14.
Oh, no,
it's going to be named after
some snack or baked good,
isn't it?
Well, tell us,
what are they?
Um, okay.
If it's a boy,
it's Daniel.
And if it's a girl?
I don't want to say.
Oh, just tell us.
We're not going to want it.
Okay.
It's Emma.
( gasps ):
Emma.
See, I don't want it.
Take it.
What?
She's clearly
an Emma.
Oh, honey, but you
love that name.
Yeah, but
I love you more.
Besides, you know
nothing goes with Bing,
so I'm screwed.
Yoo-hoo.
Aaron Litman-Garelnick
would like to say hello
to his future bride.
Oh.
( gasps )
Wow, he kind of takes your
breath away, doesn't he?
He's a keeper.
How you feeling?
Oh, you know,
I'm fi-ne.
Can I just say
I really admire
what you're doing.
Just raising her
all alone.
Oh, I'm not doing it alone.
I have Ross.
Oh, sure, now.
But what happens when
he meets somebody else
and he gets married?
Well, then he gets a divorce.
It's Ross.
I'm telling you, Rachel,
listen to Janice.
They all say they're
going to be there
until they start
their real family.
Well, I... I...
that's never
going to happen with Ross.
That's what I thought
about my first husband.
Now I'm lucky if my kid
gets to spend the weekend
with her father and the twins
and little Miss New Boobs.
Really?
Yeah.
I hate to be the one
to say it
but, honey, you two
are on your own.
Well...
that's, you know, that's...
we've been alone for the last
20 minutes and we're doing okay.
Besides,
you know what?
Maybe we won't be alone
'cause lately
things have been happening
between me and Ross, you know?
And right before
I went into labor
we, we had this kiss.
You know?
So, it might be
the beginning of something.
Hey, Janice.
Oh, hi.
Oh.
Who's this little guy-ah-y?
Say hello to Aaron.
Your future son-in-law.
Oh, no, no.
I'm going
to leave you three alone.
Oh, okay.
Bye, Janice.
Man, you see the kid
on that nose?
Uh-huh.
( groaning )
You know what I was,
uh, I was thinking about?
Huh?
Um...
that kiss before
we left the apartment.
That was,
that was something, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, it really was.
But we, we got to be careful.
We, you know, we can't let that
happen again, you know?
Right.
I mean, we don't want to go
down that road, do we?
No, no, of course not, no.
That's why I brought it up.
They didn't have any sodas?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I was talking to this nurse,
completely forgot.
And so it begins.
She in there?
Yeah, she's putting
her down now.
That's her.
Look at Emma.
I just
can't decide
who she looks more like--
you or Rachel.
What are you kidding?
She's gorgeous.
It's all Rachel.
I'm sorry.
For the last time
why aren't you two
together again?
( sighs )
No, I know, I know.
Because you're not
"in that place."
Which would be fine,
except you totally are.
It's, it's complicated,
okay?
Yeah, that's true.
You love her,
you always have
you have a child together.
There's no right answer.
Look, we've been
together, okay?
And then apart,
and then together.
And then apart.
And now we have a baby.
Mm-hmm.
It's just, if-if we
got together again
and it didn't work out...
I can never do that
to Emma.
( crying ):
I mean, she, she came
into this world
thinking everything...
Oh, now me.
What, do they
put something
in the water
in this place?
It's just, Rachel
and I, we're doing...
we're doing
really well right now.
I know, I know.
I know.
And if you try
to make it more
you might
wreck it.
Yeah, exactly.
Or you might get everything
you've wanted since you were 15.
( knocking at door )
Hey.
Hi.
I just saw a woman
breast-feeding
both of her twins
at the same time.
It is like
a freak show up here.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What is it, hey?
Really,
it's nothing.
Rach, come on, what?
I've just been thinking
about how my baby and I
are going to be all alone.
What are you talking about,
alone?
What about Ross?
Oh, please.
He'll be with his real family--
the twins
and little Miss New Boobs.
Okay, how long was I
watching that woman?
I'm just saying that,
you know...
someday Ross is
going to meet somebody
and he's going to have
his own life.
Right?
I guess so.
Yeah.
I just never thought
I'd be raising this baby
all by myself.
( sighs )
That's pretty dumb, huh?
Hey, you listen to me.
Listen to me.
You are never, ever
going to be alone.
Okay, I promise.
I won't let that happen.
Oh, Joey.
Oh, sweetie, what would
I do without you?
Hey, you don't have to
worry about that, okay?
Oh, honey
could you grab me
my other box of tissues?
They're right on that chair
under Ross' coat.
Sure.
Oh, my God.
Joey.
Oh, my God!
Okay.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
( both sighing )
That was amazing.
I know.
( sighs )
Hey... do you
realize that...
we may have just changed
our lives forever?
We may have just
started our family.
Nine months from now,
we could be here
having our own baby.
And if not,
we got to do it on a bucket.